A lot of analysis you do might relate to dates and times.
很多你的分析可能與日期和時間有關。
For instance, finding the average number of sales over a given period,
例如，在一段給定的時間，找到銷售平均次數。
selecting a list of products to data mine if they were purchased in a given period,
選擇產品列表，來做資料數據挖掘，用在特定時期內的購買數據，
or trying to find the period with the most activity in online discussion
或試圖找到最活躍的時期在線上討論
forum systems.
論壇系統。
In this course, we're not going to delve too deeply into time series analysis, but
在這課程中，我們不打算深入研究時間序列分析，但
I wanted to show you some of the basics in Python.
我想給你看Python中的一些基本的知識。
First, you should be aware that date and
首先，你應該意識到該日期和
times can be stored in many different ways.
時間的存儲有許多不同的方式。
One of the most common legacy methods for storing the date and
用於存儲日期最常用的傳統方法之一，
time in online transactions systems is based on the offset from the epoch,
時間在網上交易系統是基於從纪元的偏移量
which is January 1, 1970.
這個纪元是1970年1月1日。
There's a lot of historical cruft around this, but it's not uncommon to see systems
這裡有很多歷史記錄，但並不罕見看到
storing the date of a transaction in seconds or milliseconds since this date.
系統存儲自該日期起的交易時間（用秒或毫秒）。
So if you see large numbers where you expect to see date and time,
所以如果你看到很大的數字，而你希望看到日期和時間，
you'll need to convert them to make much sense out of the data.
你需要轉換它們，使數據變得有意義。
In Python, you can get the current time since the epoch using the time module.
在Python中，你可以獲得從纪元計算來的目前時間，使用時間模組。
You can then create a time stamp using the from time stamp function
然後，可以創建時間戳記，使用'從時間戳記函數'
on the date time object.
在日期時間的物件。
When we print this value out, we see that the year, month, day, and so
當我們列印出此值時，我們看到，年、月、日，等等
forth are also printed out.
還會列印出來。
The date time object has handy attributes to get the representative hour, day,
日期時間物件都具有方便的特性，來代表小時，一天，
seconds, etc.
秒，等等。
Date time objects allow for simple math using time deltas.
日期時間物件允許簡單的數學，運用時間增量。
For instance, here, we can create a time delta of 100 days,
例如在這裡，我們可以創建100天的時間增量，
then do subtraction and comparisons with the date time object.
然後做日期時間物件的減法和比較。
This is commonly used in data science for creating sliding windows.
這是常用在資料科學裡，來創建可調整的視窗。
For instance, where you might want to look for
例如，在那裡你可能想要尋找
any five day span of time where sales were highest, and flag that for follow up.
任何五天跨度的時間銷售額最高，然後標示它為進一步探究。
This is just a little glimpse at dates and times in Python.
這只是Python中的日期和時間的一點點提示。
In week three of this course, we're going to investigate dates and
在本課程的第三週，我們將調查日期和
times a bit more using the pandas date time library.
時間多一點，使用Pandas的日期時間程式庫。